Welcome to Expense Agent video series.
In this video, we'll try to explain you
what is coming related to new countries
and new languages.
So,
uh from the very beginning, uh we had uh
availability in English language only
and United States from um actually from
May, but now with July, we are extending
to new languages and new countries. So,
we'll have Danish, French, German,
Spanish language availability uh
from the July, but also we will extend
to new countries: Austria, Denmark,
France, Germany, Spain, UK, and Europe.
In North America, after US, we'll extend
to Canada and in APAC, Australia and New
Zealand. So, you'll see more and more
countries is coming. So, only 2 months
after first release, we have uh new
countries and new languages and more
countries and languages to come in
October. So, now let's see how it works
in different language.
>> Thank you, Alexander. Let me just show
you how it works in Danish.
So, here I am in the web experience for
dedicated expense management for the
submitters.
Uh and in my browser, I have the local
language set up for Danish. And you can
see that all the strings are already
translated in Danish and all the
categories and subcategories can be
supported in Danish environment. So, in
here, I can just go ahead and upload a
receipt, and this receipt can also
support multiple languages. Even though
the environment and the local language
here is Danish, it can support any other
language in this environment because of
course, when you travel, you travel uh
or you can also travel abroad outside
the Denmark. Let me show you the
existing receipts that the Expense Agent
has already processed.
So, let's take this one.
In here, the Expense Agent has scanned
the PDF receipt that we are going to see
now,
which is completely in a Danish
language.
And then it has successfully extracted
all the information from the receipt and
also done the categorization correctly.
So, uh you can see that it works
smoothly also in different languages
with the support of different
uh different
uh currencies and also with uh different
categories.
>> I thank you, Monika. Thank you for for
showing you guys how it looks like in a
Danish language. We cannot show all
languages uh in this short video, but we
wanted to uh show two examples. So, I
will switch to Spanish language. So, you
can see my user experience is now in a
Spanish. And if I upload
my two
new receipts,
both of them are in Spanish, but I will
already show what I have uploaded here.
So,
I already have one train ticket from um
Spain.
So, if I open
this PDF,
it details this is
a train ticket for Barcelona.
So, system already processed all details
about category and all these details.
So, now if I look back,
in the meantime,
my Expense Agent already uh completed
with uh not only uploaded my categories
extraction and categorization all
details about my two receipts. So, if I
look into this one,
this is Tapa Tapa Bar,
a restaurant. So, system
properly understood that this is about
meal.
And another one, hotel.
So, if I look
to details,
you will see
this is
hotel receipt,
Spanish.
So, what system already did, understood
which hotel is, all details about
uh dates, that this [snorts] is uh
four nights in Barcelona.
Categorization is uh properly hotel, but
even again we have details, so we have
all itemizations, uh uh, everything in a
Spanish. So, everything is there and
only what we need, we need to confirm
and after reviewing all of them, I need
to submit and everything will fine.
Okay, this is what we wanted to show in
this video. We show, uh, examples in two
different languages, but as we already
said, it works right now fully supported
in five new languages and more to come
in October. But, what we wanted to
emphasize, we tested, uh, this agent
with receipts in almost all possible
languages and letters around the world.
So, it works with all languages, but in
this moment, this is fully supported for
these five languages and as I said, more
languages will come.
Thank you for watching this video.
>> Thank you.